# **Juhwan Lee**

Cell: 360-593-6736 · ljh1230vvv@gmail.com · juhwan@pdx.edu · https://www.linkedin.com/in/juhwan-lee/

#### **SUMMARY**

Enthusiastic software engineer with extensive technical experience in software testing and full-stack web development in a professional team environment. Familiar with data structures, object-oriented programming, systems programming, algorithms, and relational databases. Successfully work in teams and self-directed settings with the ability to quickly learn and master new technologies.

### **WORK EXPERIENCE**

FASOO Software Engineer Intern Seoul, South Korea Jun 2022 - Aug 2022

- Worked as part of a four-member team under the Wrapsody Development team for the internship project called Wrapsody eCo Workspace
- Designed and implemented a new collaborative workspace, where users can freely share their opinions, in Wrapsody eCo by integrating a real-time open-source collaborative text editor called Etherpad
- Presented Wrapsody eCo Workspace in front of the CEO, team leaders, and senior developers on the last day
  of the internship
- Technologies used: React.js · MySQL · JavaScript · TypeScript · Node.js · Microsoft Visual Studio Code · Git

MEDIAZEN
Software Engineer Intern

Seoul, South Korea Jun 2021 - Sep 2021

- Suggested new application ideas for STT, TTS, NLU, and Computer Vision in front of the team leader and senior developers on the first week of the internship
- Created 1000 test scenarios for the advancement of ART (Automatic Recognition Test), a software testing automation tool
- Responsible for software testing of the Volkswagen Voice Control System and reporting test results to the project manager when a new version is released
- Technologies used: Python · Microsoft Office · C++ · Linux · Microsoft Visual Studio Code

**REPUBLIC OF KOREA NAVY** 

South Korea

### **Petty Officer Second Class, Administrative Clerk**

Jan 2018 - Oct 2019

- In charge of reporting the personnel status of the FF-956 to the fleet, flotilla, and squadron
- Assisted in administrative work in the secretary's office of the vice chief of naval operations

#### **EDUCATION**

#### **PORTLAND STATE UNIVERSITY**

Portland, Oregon Jan 2020 - Mar 2023

## **Bachelor of Science in Computer Science**

• Overall GPA: 3.54 / 4.00

- Activities and societies: Software Engineering Capstone Team Lead
- Academic honors: President's List (Winter 2022), Dean's List (Spring 2022)
- Relevant courses: Data Structures, Object-Oriented Programming, Systems Programming, Software Engineering, Operating Systems, Algorithms and Complexity, Relational Databases, Web Development
- Software engineering capstone project: Implement a cross-platform fitness challenge application called Walktober that is integrated with built-in iOS and Android fitness tracking systems

## PORTLAND STATE UNIVERSITY

Portland, Oregon Sep 2015 - Jun 2017

#### **Bachelor of Science in Mechanical Engineering**

- Academic honors: International Achievement Scholarships (\$12,000)
- Leave of absence: Korean mandatory military service (Jun 2017 Jan 2020)

#### **SKILLS**

**Technologies:** C, C++, Python, Java, JavaScript, TypeScript, React, HTML, CSS, SQL, Node.js, Linux, Vim, VScode, Git **Languages:** Native in Korean, Fluent in English